1.63. AND THE S&P 500 OFF BY
1.16. MANULIFE UNVEILED A NEW
EXPANSION STRATEGY. THE
CANADIAN INSURANCE AND
INVESTING GIANT IS LAUNCHING
THE MANULIFE LONGEVITY
INSTITUTE, WHICH PROVIDE
RESEARCH AND INVESTMENT
PLATFORM BACKED BY A $350
MILLION COMMITMENT THROUGH 2030.
THE COMPANY IS ALSO EXPANDING
ITS FOOTPRINT IN INDIA THROUGH
A PARTNERSHIP WITH MAHINDRA AND
MAHINDRA TO ENTER THE INDIAN
INSURANCE MARKET. LET'S HEAR
MORE FROM THIS FROM PHIL
WITHERINGTON. HE IS THE
PRESIDENT AND CEO OF MANULIFE
FINANCIAL CORPORATION. PHIL,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR JOINING
US TODAY.
>> WELL THANK YOU, ROGER. IT'S
GREAT TO BE HERE.
>> YOU'VE GOT A BUSY SCHEDULE.
LET'S TALK FIRST ABOUT INDIA,
THE EXPANSION THERE. WHAT HAS
YOU EYEING INDIA AND THIS NEW
AGREEMENT YOU'VE COME TO.
>> WELL ROGER THIS IS
INCREDIBLY EXCITING. MANULIFE
AS PART OF OUR REFRESH STRATEGY
THAT WE HAVE LAUNCHED JUST TWO
DAYS AGO, WE HAVE EXPRESSED OUR
INTENTION TO ENTER THE INDIA
INSURANCE MARKET WITH A PARTNER,
MAHINDRA OF INDIA. THEY ARE A
WELL KNOWN, WELL ESTABLISHED,
VERY STRONG, STRONGLY BRANDED
CONGLOMERATE IN INDIA. AND THE
WAY WE SEE IT IS THAT THERE ARE
REALLY THREE MEGA ECONOMIES OF
THE NEXT GENERATION THE US,
CHINA AND INDIA. AND IN OUR
EXISTING BUSINESS, WE HAVE
STRONG SCALE AND PROFITABLE
BUSINESSES IN THE US AND CHINA.
BUT WE IDENTIFIED INDIA AS A
MARKET WHERE WE HAD A
RELATIVELY SMALLER PRESENCE. WE
HAVE AN EXISTING ASSET
MANAGEMENT PARTNERSHIP WITH
MAHINDRA, AND EFFECTIVELY WHAT
WE'RE DOING IS WE'RE BUILDING
ON THAT PARTNERSHIP TO ENTER
LIFE INSURANCE AS A COMPLEMENT
TO OUR ASSET MANAGEMENT
OPERATIONS. THAT GIVES US THEN
A PRESENCE IN BOTH INSURANCE
AND ASSET MANAGEMENT IN ALL
THREE MEGA ECONOMIES OF THE
FUTURE. AND THIS IS SOMETHING
WE'RE INCREDIBLY EXCITED ABOUT.
>> AND NOW WITH INDIA, ANY
CONCERNS CANADA AND US OR
CANADA AND INDIA? EXCUSE ME.
RELATIONS HAVE BEEN STRAINED.
THEY SEEM TO BE EASING. WE SAW
AN AGREEMENT REACHED WHEN IT
CAME TO MINERALS TODAY. ANY
CONCERNS THAT THAT COULD PLAY A
ROLE IF THIS IF THE
RELATIONSHIP SUDDENLY GOES
SOUTH AGAIN.
>> WELL I THINK IT'S FANTASTIC
THAT GREAT CANADIAN COMPANIES
AND I DO CONSIDER MANULIFE TO
BE A TRUE CANADIAN INSTITUTION,
A NATIONAL CHAMPION. I THINK
IT'S GREAT THAT WE CAN BE
OUTWARDS LOOKING INTERNATIONAL
IN OUR EXPANSION, AND THAT
PROVIDES MANY SOURCES OF GROWTH
OPPORTUNITY, AND THAT'S GREAT
FOR CANADIANS. IT CREATES JOBS
HERE IN CANADA. IT'S GREAT FOR
CANADIAN INVESTORS. WE REMIT
CAPITAL FROM AROUND THE WORLD
BACK TO CANADA. AND SO I THINK
I'M INCREDIBLY PROUD THAT
MANULIFE CAN BE A HUGELY
INTERNATIONAL AND DIVERSIFIED
FINANCIAL SERVICE CENTRE,
FINANCIAL SERVICE GROUP THAT IS
HEADQUARTERED HERE IN CANADA.
>> BUT OPTIMISTIC ABOUT INDIA,
NOT CONCERNED ABOUT ANY
POTENTIAL HEADWINDS FROM THAT.
>> I'M VERY OPTIMISTIC. I MEAN,
ONE OF THE REASONS WHY WE'RE
MOVING NOW AND WE'VE HAD OUR
EYE ON THE INDIA INSURANCE
MARKET FOR MANY YEARS. WE SEE
FAVOURABLE DEVELOPMENTS FROM A
REGULATORY PERSPECTIVE. WE SEE
RAPIDLY GROWING WEALTH IN INDIA.
AND YOU KNOW, WE'VE GOT THE
RIGHT PARTNER THROUGH MAHINDRA.
AND SO THIS FEELS LIKE THE
RIGHT TIME. I'M OPTIMISTIC
ABOUT INDIA. I'M EXCITED ABOUT
THE OPPORTUNITIES IN CHINA AND
ACROSS ASIA. AND I'M ALSO
OPTIMISTIC ABOUT THE
OPPORTUNITIES HERE IN OUR HOME
MARKET OF CANADA AND THE US. WE
HAVE A GREAT FOOTPRINT AROUND
THE WORLD.
>> ALL RIGHT. LET'S TALK ABOUT
ASIA. I THINK 26%. WAS THAT HOW
MUCH.
>> 29% CORE EARNINGS GROWTH.
YEAH.
>> WHAT WHAT FUELLED THAT IN
ASIA.
>> WELL IN RECENT YEARS WE'VE
SEEN TREMENDOUS GROWTH FROM OUR
ASIA MARKETS. AND YOU KNOW IF I
JUST LOOK OVER THE PAST COUPLE
OF YEARS, THE VALUE OF NEW
INSURANCE SALES, WE USE A
METRIC CALLED NEW BUSINESS
CONTRACTUAL SERVICE MARGIN.
IT'S A MEASURE OF THE VALUE
THAT WE GET FROM NEW SALES
THAT'S BEEN GROWING IN EXCESS
OF 30%. AND SO IT'S ABSOLUTELY
LOGICAL THAT EARNINGS FOLLOW
THROUGH. AND WE'RE SEEING
EARNINGS GROWTH THIS QUARTER OF
29% YEAR ON YEAR AND YEAR TO
DATE IN ASIA. WE'VE SEEN STRONG
DOUBLE DIGIT GROWTH IN 2025.
AND THAT'S FOLLOWS STRONG
DOUBLE DIGIT GROWTH IN 2024 AS
WELL. AND IF I LOOK AT THE
PERFORMANCE OVER THE COURSE OF
THE LAST QUARTER, IT REALLY
REFLECTS THE DIVERSIFIED NATURE
OF OUR BUSINESS ACROSS ASIA.
WE'VE SEEN STRONG GROWTH IN
CHINA. WE'VE SEEN STRONG GROWTH
IN SINGAPORE AND CONTINUED
VALUE GENERATION FROM KEY
MARKETS SUCH AS HONG KONG.
>> SO IT'S BEEN A GOOD SWING
FOR YOU. NOW, YOU DID GET SOME
SOME ADVANTAGE FROM SOME LOWER
TAXES, CREDIT RECOVERIES THAT
ARE GONE NOW. WHAT HOW WILL
THAT HAVE AN IMPACT.
>> YEAH, THERE WERE SOME
FAVOURABLE ITEMS THAT MOVED IN
OUR FAVOUR IN THE THIRD QUARTER.
BUT EVEN WHEN WE STRIP THOSE
ITEMS OUT IT'S A VERY STRONG
QUARTER. SO WHEN I THINK ABOUT
THE QUARTERLY RESULTS, IT'S
BEEN YET ANOTHER QUARTER FOR
MANULIFE OF STRONG OPERATING
AND FINANCIAL RESULTS. AND I
THINK THAT IS UNDERPINNED BY
THE ROBUST SALES AND GROWTH IN
ASSET ASSETS UNDER MANAGEMENT
IN WEALTH AND ASSET MANAGEMENT
BUSINESS, AND IT REALLY GIVES
ME A GREAT DEAL OF CONFIDENCE
IN THE FUTURE. AND I THINK THAT
REALLY SPEAKS TO WHY THIS IS
THE RIGHT TIME FOR US TO UNVEIL
OUR REFRESHED STRATEGY THAT
SETS MANULIFE UP NOT JUST FOR
THE SHORT TERM, NOT JUST TO
DELIVER ON OUR NEAR-TERM
TARGETS THAT WE REMAIN
CONFIDENT IN DELIVERING, BUT
ACTUALLY SET MANULIFE UP FOR
THE NEXT TEN YEARS AND BEYOND.
AND THAT'S BEEN THE LENS THAT
OUR ORGANISATION HAS APPLIED IN
REFRESHING OUR STRATEGY.
>> AND LET'S TALK ONE OF THE
OTHER ONES. YOU'RE BRINGING IN
LONGEVITY, THE LONGEVITY
PROGRAM. TOUCH A LITTLE BIT ON
THAT AND EXPLAIN THAT.
>> RIGHT. SO THE LONGEVITY
INSTITUTE THIS IS A 350 MILLION
CANADIAN DOLLAR COMMITMENT TO
ADVANCE RESEARCH, ADVOCACY AND
COMMUNITY INVESTMENT SO THAT WE
CAN HELP PEOPLE LIVE LONGER,
HEALTHIER AND MORE FINANCIALLY
SECURE LIVES. AND THIS IS
SOMETHING THAT IS VERY CLOSELY
CONNECTED TO OUR STRATEGY. ONE
OF THE STRATEGIC PRIORITIES
THAT WE HAVE IDENTIFIED IN OUR
STRATEGIC REFRESH IS REALLY
ABOUT EMPOWERING OUR CUSTOMERS
TO LIVE HEALTHIER, LONGER AND
MORE FINANCIALLY SECURE LIVES.
AND THIS IS TOTALLY ALIGNED.
BUT WE FEEL WE CAN HAVE AN
IMPACT BEYOND OUR CUSTOMERS ON
THE BROADER COMMUNITY.
>> AND HOW DOES THAT BENEFIT
MANULIFE?
>> WELL, IT'S ABSOLUTELY IN OUR
INTERESTS FOR OUR CUSTOMERS TO
LIVE LONGER. AND I THINK THIS
IS, YOU KNOW, THIS IS WHERE WE
CAN PUT OUR MONEY, WHERE OUR
MOUTH IS, THAT WE WANT MANULIFE
CUSTOMERS NOT ONLY TO LIVE
LONGER, BUT WE WANT THEM TO
HAVE LONGER HEALTH SPANS. SO
LIVE LONGER IN THE HEALTHY
PHASE OF LIFE AND THEN HAVE THE
SHORTEST POSSIBLE PERIODS OF
ILL HEALTH. AND WHEN THEY DO
HAVE ILL HEALTH, WE WANT TO BE
THERE FOR THEM. SO I THINK THIS
IS A GREAT EXAMPLE OF HOW WE
CAN TURN THE INSURANCE INDUSTRY
ON ITS HEAD AND ACTUALLY
PROMOTE HEALTH AND WELLNESS,
RATHER THAN ONLY THINK ABOUT A
TRANSACTIONAL LIFE INSURANCE
CONTRACT.
>> AND JUST KIND OF A BIG, BIG,
BIG PICTURE QUESTION. WE'VE
SEEN SOME TURMOIL IN THE
MARKETS, A LITTLE BIT CONCERNS
ABOUT AI EVALUATION. WHERE DO
YOU SEE YOURSELF? WHERE DO YOU
SEE MANULIFE GOING THROUGH ALL
THIS OVER THE NEXT FEW MONTHS?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, WHEN I LOOK
AT OUR STOCK PRICE AND OUR
PERFORMANCE, YES, I'M VERY
PROUD. BUT IT'S REALLY A
REFLECTION OF THE THE PERIOD OF
TRANSFORMATION THE ORGANISATION
HAS BEEN THROUGH THAT REFLECTS
DISCIPLINED EXECUTION,
DISCIPLINED MANAGEMENT OF
CAPITAL AND CLEAR STRATEGIC
PRIORITIES. AND OUR OBJECTIVE
IS TO MAKE SURE THAT WHEN WE
LOOK AT THIS NEXT CHAPTER FOR
MANULIFE, WE HAVE REALLY CLEAR
PRIORITIES, NOT JUST FOR THE
NEXT COUPLE OF YEARS, BUT FOR
THE NEXT DECADE AND BEYOND. AND
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT WE'VE DONE
WITH THIS STRATEGY REVAMP AND
THE ENTRY INTO NEW MARKETS SUCH
AS INDIA.
>> ALL RIGHT, PHIL, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH FOR JOINING US TO